export const quizzes = {
    1:{
        quizTitle: "Test 1 Algebra",
        questions: [
    {
      question: "1+1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["11", "2", "1", "0"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "-1-1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["2", "-2", "0", "-1"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "10x1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["1", "10", "11", "20"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },{
      question: "-9+10",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["19", "1", "-1", "-19"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    }]
    },
    2:{
        quizTitle: "Test 2 Algebra",
        questions: [
    {
      question: "1+1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["11", "2", "1", "0"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "-1-1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["2", "-2", "0", "-1"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "10x1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["1", "10", "11", "20"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },{
      question: "-9+10",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["19", "1", "-1", "-19"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    }]
    },
    3:{
        quizTitle: "Test 3 Algebra",
        questions: [
    {
      question: "1+1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["11", "2", "1", "0"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "-1-1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["2", "-2", "0", "-1"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "10x1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["1", "10", "11", "20"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },{
      question: "-9+10",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["19", "1", "-1", "-19"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    }]
    },
    4:{
        quizTitle: "Test 4 Algebra",
        questions: [
    {
      question: "1+1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["11", "2", "1", "0"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "-1-1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["2", "-2", "0", "-1"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },
    {
      question: "10x1=",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["1", "10", "11", "20"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    },{
      question: "-9+10",
      questionType: "text",
      answerSelectionType: "single",
      answers: ["19", "1", "-1", "-19"],
      point: "25",
      correctAnswer: "2"
    }]}
    };